Karim Abdelhalim

Web & Mobile application developer

SUMMARY

I am a passionate self-taught front-end developer. I love coding creative UIs and bringing designs to life with clean, efficient code. My expertise includes building responsive and user-friendly websites and applications, constantly learning and adapting to new technologies and trends to deliver the best digital experiences.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer at MedC

OCT 2023 - 2024

Collaborated with a skilled team to deliver a medical educational app, focusing on enhancing the user interface and experience.

- Development of Mobile application UI
- Enhancements on website

Front-end Developer at Ringfill

DEC 2023 - 2024

Contributed to both frontend and backend development for various tasks such as:

- Development of Mobile application UI
- Enhancements on website

COURSEES & TRAININGS

DEPI | React Development

April 2024 - OCT2024

Ministry of communications Information, Egypt

- Cloud computing | web development (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript)
- Front-end development (React.js, Tailwind CSS)
- Back-end development (node.js, Express.js, MongoDB)
- Soft Skills

Front-end Development

2023

Almenor Platform

- Web development using HTML5 & CSS3
- Mastering CSS flex, CSS Grid & CSS Animation
- JavaScript for expert levels
- Git & GitHub

PROJECTS

Babel library

- Description: A library app that offers a diverse collection of books, each with comprehensive information. It includes features such as a search bar, the ability to add books to your favorites, a reading progress tracker, and a dedicated screen for adding your favorite quotes.
- Technologies: Next.js, tailwind CSS, Shadon UI, React Native (expo), firebase, Figma
- Links: GitHub

UnityCare hospital

- Description: This platform was developed to provide a comprehensive solution for healthcare services. It allows patients to easily book appointments, access information about doctors and specialties, and stay informed with the latest medical news. The website is designed to be scalable, secure, and user-friendly.
- Technologies: Next.js, TypeScript, tailwind CSS, Shadcn UI, node.js, MongoDB
- Links: GitHub Web Page

CONTACTS

Phone: (+20) 102 309 6263 **Address**: Egypt, Cairo

Email: Karimoda66@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/karim248

GitHub: https://github.com/Karim248119 **Portfolio**: https://karim-a-hassan.vercel.app

EDUCATION

ASU Mechanical engineering (Mechatronic department)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programing Languages

- HTML
- Type Script
- CSS
- PythonC++
- Java Scripts

Front-end

- React.js
- Next.js
- Shadcn UI
- React Native

Back-end

- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB

Version Control

- Git
- GitHub

Design/Prototyping

Figma

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Native)

English